[text "R"] slides in from the left 37px (slide+fade), ease-out, 600ms
[text "emembering"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~104ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 20px, ease-out
[text "is so"] slides in from the right 21px (slide+fade), ease-out, 300ms
[text "Remembering s so"] slides out to the left 47px (slide), ease-out
[text "vesterday"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~42ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 113px, ease-out
[text "vesterday"] slides out to the right 22px (slide), ease-out
[text "Meet"] pops out
[text "your"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~67ms apart (fade), ease-out
[text "New"] fades in as one block, linear, 400ms
[text "your"] slides out up-left 223px (slide), ease-out
[text "app"] slides in rising 128px (slide), linear, 433ms
[text "notes"] slides in rising 53px (slide), linear, 434ms
[text "second"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~56ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 261px, ease-out
[text "brain"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~117ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 91px, ease-out
[text "es pp"] slides out to the left 158px (slide), ease-out
[text "thought partner"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~93ms apart (slide), each sliding from the right 252px, ease-out
[text "econd brain"] slides out to the left 246px (slide), ease-out
[text "hought artner"] slides out down-left 152px (slide), ease-out
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Capture anything"] pops in
[text "apture anything"] slides out to the right 9px (slide), linear
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Turn brain dumps into beautiful notes"] letters cascade in ~139ms apart (pop), each dropping 10px, linear
[text "Turn brain dumps into beautiful"] fades out (484ms)
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Let Mem take meeting"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~33ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 79px, ease-out
[text "et Mem ta"] slides out to the left 32px (slide), ease-out
[text "notes for you"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~67ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 36px, ease-out
[text "for you"] slides out to the right 33px (slide), ease-out
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Tel"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~34ms apart (slide+fade), each rising 50px, ease-out
[text "Tel"] pops out
[text "Tell"] pops in
[text "ell"] pops out
[text "needtoask aboutthedomain name Ined"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~89ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 135px, ease-in
[text "need to ask about the domain name"] slides out upward 38px (slide), ease-in
[text "eed"] slides out up-left 61px (slide), ease-out
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Mem"] slides in rising 13px (slide+fade), ease-out, 133ms
[text "remembers"] slides in up-left 22px (slide), ease-out, 400ms
[text "membe"] slides out to the left 10px (slide), ease-out
[text "Mem"] slides out to the left 23px (slide), ease-out
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "Find"] slides in from the right 13px (slide), ease-out, 133ms
[text "Find"] slides out to the right 36px (slide), linear
[text "DeepSearch"] letters cascade in right-to-left ~8ms apart (slide+fade), linear
[text "Deep Search"] leaves at hard cut
[cut] hard cut
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "d"] slides in from the right 105px (slide), ease-in, 1168ms
[text "an"] slides in from the right 51px (slide+fade), ease-out, 200ms
[text "recall"] fades in as one block, ease-out, 233ms
[text "and recall"] fades out (167ms)
[text "everything with"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~52ms apart (slide+fade), ease-out
[text "everything"] slides out to the left 12px (slide), ease-in
[text "Mem Chat"] fades in as one block, ease-out, 634ms
[text "Mem Chat"] fades out (200ms)
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)
[text "I've created a to-do list for you"] letters cascade in ~33ms apart (slide+fade), each rising 27px, ease-out
[text "created a to-do list for you"] slides out to the left 30px (slide), linear
[text "and of course"] pops in
[text "and of course"] slides out to the left 17px (slide), ease-out
[text "Offline Mode"] slides in from the left 15px (slide), ease-out, 200ms
[text "Tea haing"] slides in up-right 40px (slide), linear, 400ms
[text "Offline Mode"] slides out upward 41px (slide), linear
[text "Team Sharing"] pops out
[text "Templates"] slides in rising 31px (slide), ease-out, 400ms
[text "Templates"] pops out
[text "API Acess"] pops in
[text "API Access"] pops out
[text "Dark Mode"] letters cascade in ~181ms apart (pop), each rising 16px, linear
[text "Dark Mode"] pops out
[text "Not"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~184ms apart (slide), each sliding from the right 116px, ease-out
[text "another"] slides in from the right 60px (slide+fade), ease-out, 400ms
[text "notes app"] letters cascade in left-to-right ~25ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the right 32px, linear
[text "Not another notes"] slides out upward 23px (slide), ease-out
[text "Your go-to thought partner"] letters cascade in right-to-left ~79ms apart (slide+fade), each sliding from the left 22px, ease-out
[text "Your go-to thought partner"] slides out to the left 10px (slide), linear
[product demo] embedded app footage (not transcribed)